immunotec.com 2019-03-21

# 

                                               PRIVACY POLICY
Immunotec, Inc. (also referred to as “we,” “our,” “us”) has one goal:
To provide high quality scientifically based nutrition and wellness products which enhance quality of life and
performance. We thrive by empowering people to share an exceptional network marketing opportunity
accessible to everyone. We commit to continued growth and prosperity for our Consultants, Employees,
and Stakeholders.
    1.  What Information Do We Gather?
    2.  What Do We Do With the Information We Collect?
    3.  Who Can Use the Information We Collect and How?
    4.   How Do We Protect the Personal Information We Collect?
    5.   What Are Your Rights Regarding Your Personal Data?
    6.   How Do You Opt-out of Personal Information Sharing with Our Business Partners?
    7.   How Do You Correct and Update Your Personal Data?
    8.   What is Our Privacy Policy If You Are an Underage Child?
    9.   What Happens When You Link to a Third-Party Web Site?
    10.  What Happens When We Update Our Privacy Policy?
    11.  Your European Union Privacy Rights
    12.  Your California Privacy Rights
    13.  What Else Do You Need To Know?
    14.  What If You Have Questions?
1.       What Information Do We Gather?
When you visit our Website and Portal (“Site”), we collect only the information and personal data you
have agreed to provide to us that is necessary to identify your needs and to provide you with better service.
Through your use of the site or registration as a new user, we may request personal data including, but
not limited to:
             •   Name, company and job title
             •   Contact information including email address and cell phone number
             •   Demographic information including postal code, product preferences and interests
             •   Internet Protocol (“IP”) Address and other persistent identifiers
             •   Other information relevant to customer surveys and offers
             •   If you become a registered user or if you conduct transactions through this website, we
                 will collect information about the transactions you engage in while on the website and
                 your other activity on the site. This information may include, without limitation, areas of
                 the website that you visit, transaction type, content that you view, download or submit,
                 transaction amount, payment, and billing information as well as the nature, quantity and
                 price of the goods or services you exchange and the individuals or entities with whom you
                 communicate or transact business.

Some of this personal data, including name, company and contact information, will only be collected if
you voluntarily provide it during the user registration process. We may also track information such as the
domain name and the name of the web page from which you entered our Site, and how much time you
spend on each of our pages. We collect information that is combined with other web visitors' information,
such as how many times visitors click on each web page and the methods by which our Site was found.
We may collect IP addresses and website usage information from you when you visit our Site via the use
of "cookies." An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you are using your
browser on the Internet.
A cookie is a small file that is stored on the hard drive of your computer ready for future access when you
return to our Site. We use cookies to deliver web content specific to you and to keep track of your online
order activity. Cookies cannot pass viruses, harm your computer or pass on private information such as
an email address without the computer user's intervention. Cookies contain session identification
numbers that allow our systems to recall previous sessions for authentication efforts and assemble
information from our gathered data. You can configure your computer's browser to alert you when a site
is attempting to send you a cookie and allow you to accept or refuse the cookie. Further information on
how to prevent cookies from being stored on your device can be found on
http://www.allaboutcookies.org under the ‘manage cookies’ section. Alternatively, you can access
further information by going to the help menu within your internet browser. To opt out of being tracked
by Google Analytics across all websites visit http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
We use cookies to give you the best experience on our website. If you continue without changing your
cookie settings, we assume that you consent to our use of cookies on this device. You can change your
cookie settings at any time but if you do, you may lose some functionality on our website.
2.       What Do We Do With the Personal Information We Collect?
You will be asked to provide personal data in certain fields on this Site that allow you to be able to use our
Services. The personal data we collect is used only for the purpose we state at the time of collection or
for purposes contained below. For example, our uses may include, but are not limited to, the following:
     •   To process transactions. Immunotec, Inc. uses personal data such as name, physical address,
         telephone number, email address, and company/institution to engage in interactions with you,
         including contacting you about your transactions with the site.
     •   To process payments. We use financial/credit card and payment information to process your
         order and may need to share some of this information with delivery services, credit card clearing
         houses, and other third parties to complete the transaction.
     •   To provide support or other services. Immunotec, Inc. may use your personal data to provide you
         with support or other services that you have ordered or requested. Immunotec, Inc. may also use
         your personal information to respond directly to your requests for information, including
         registrations for newsletters, webinars, or other specific requests, or pass your contact
         information to the appropriate Immunotec, Inc. distributor or reseller for further follow-up
         related to your interests.
     •   To provide information based on your needs and respond to your requests. Immunotec, Inc. may
         use your personal data to provide you with notices of new product releases and service
         developments.
     •   To provide online forums and social networks. Some services available on the websites may
         permit you to participate in interactive discussions, post comments, opportunities, or other

  content to a Forum, or otherwise engage in networking activities. Some of these services may be
  moderated; all may be accessed for technical reasons (for example, for improvements or fixes).
  Immunotec, Inc. does not control the content that users post to the Forums or social networks.
  You should carefully consider whether you wish to submit personal information to these forums
  or social networks and tailor any content you submit appropriately and in accordance with the
  relevant terms of use. You should also review any additional terms and conditions that may
  govern your use of these services, including terms related to sharing your personal information
  and receiving communications.
• To administer products. Immunotec, Inc. may contact you if you purchase products to confirm
  certain information about your order (for example, that you did not experience problems in the
  download process). We may also use this information to confirm compliance with licensing and
  other terms of use and may share it with your company/institution.
• To select content, improve quality, and facilitate use of the websites. Immunotec, Inc. may use
  your personal data, including the information gathered as a result of site navigation and electronic
  protocols and cookies (including third-party cookies), to help create and personalize website
  content, improve website quality, track marketing campaign responsiveness, evaluate page
  response rates, conduct usability testing, and facilitate your use of the websites (for example, to
  facilitate navigation and the login process, avoid duplicate data entry, enhance security, keep
  track of shopping cart additions, and preserve order information between sessions).
• To serve personalized advertising to you. We don't share your personal data with advertisers
  without your consent. We allow advertisers to choose the characteristics of users who will see
  their advertisements, and we may use any of the non-personally-identifiable data attributes we
  have collected to select the appropriate audience for those advertisements. When you click on or
  otherwise interact with an advertisement, there is a possibility that the advertiser may place a
  cookie in your browser and that your attributes meet the criteria the advertiser selected.
• To assess usage of Immunotec, Inc. products and services. Immunotec, Inc. may track your usage
  of Immunotec, Inc. products and services to determine your level of usage, and those usage
  statistics may be made available to Immunotec, Inc.’s content licensors and your
  company/institution.
• To communicate with you about events. We may communicate with you about events hosted or
  co-sponsored by Immunotec, Inc. or one of our business associates. This may include information
  about the event's content, event logistics, payment, updates, and additional information related
  to the event. Information you provide when registering for or participating in a conference
  managed or co-sponsored by parties, other than or in addition to Immunotec, Inc. may be shared
  with those parties, and the treatment of such information is further subject to the privacy policies
  of those parties. Immunotec, Inc. and its conference co-sponsors may contact you after the event
  about the event, subsequent iterations of the event and related events. Please note that
  Immunotec, Inc. event organizers, co-sponsors, exhibitors, and other third parties may directly
  request your personal information at their conference booths or presentations. Providing your
  information to them is optional, and you should review their privacy policies to address your
  particular needs and concerns about how they will treat your personal information.
• To update you on relevant Immunotec, Inc. benefits, programs, and opportunities. Immunotec,
  Inc. may communicate with you regarding relevant Immunotec, Inc. benefits, programs, and
  opportunities available to you.
• To engage with third parties. Immunotec, Inc. may share your personal data with third parties in
  connection with services that these individuals or entities perform for or with Immunotec, Inc..
  These third parties are restricted from using this data in any way other than to provide services

         for Immunotec, Inc. or for the collaboration in which they and Immunotec, Inc. are contractually
         engaged (for example, hosting an Immunotec, Inc. database or engaging in data processing on
         Immunotec, Inc.’s behalf, or mailing you information that you requested). These third parties are
         carefully selected by Immunotec, Inc. and obligated to keep your data secure. From time to time,
         we may also share your information with third parties whom we think might provide content,
         products, or services of interest to you.
    •    To protect Immunotec, Inc. content and services. We may use your personal data to prevent
         potentially illegal activities and to enforce our terms and conditions. We also use a variety of
         technological systems to detect and address anomalous activity and to screen content to prevent
         abuse, such as spam. These efforts may, on occasion, result in a temporary or permanent
         suspension or termination of some functions for some users. By using the Website, you
         acknowledge and agree that we may access, retain and disclose the personal data we collect and
         maintain about you if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such access, retention
         or disclosure is reasonably necessary to: (a) comply with legal process (e.g. a subpoena or court
         order) or law; (b) enforce our Terms of Use, this Privacy Policy, or other contracts with you,
         including investigation of potential violations thereof; (c) respond to claims that any content
         violates the rights of third parties; (d) respond to your requests for customer service; and/or (e)
         protect the rights, property or personal safety of Immunotec, Inc., its agents and affiliates, its
         users and/or the public. This includes exchanging information with other companies and
         organizations for fraud protection, compliance with applicable law, and spam/malware
         prevention, and similar purposes.
    •    To get feedback or input from you. In order to deliver products and services of most interest to
         our customers, from time to time, we may ask members, customers, volunteers, and website
         visitors to provide us input and feedback (for example through surveys, usability studies, focus
         groups).
    •    To protect Immunotec, Inc. information assets as well as your own personal data. The
         Immunotec, Inc. Information Security Program protects the confidentiality, integrity, and
         availability of Immunotec, Inc. information assets by following a risk management approach based
         on policies, standards, guidelines, and procedures to meet security objectives while supporting
         business and operational goals.
    •    To assist in Business Transfers. As we continue to develop our business, we may buy, merge, or
         partner with other companies. In such transactions, (including in contemplation of such
         transactions) user information may be among the transferred assets. If a portion or all of
         Immunotec, Inc.’s assets are sold or transferred to a third-party, customer personal data
         (including your email address) would likely be one of the transferred business assets. If such
         transfer is subject to additional mandatory restrictions under applicable laws, Immunotec, Inc.
         will comply with such restrictions.
To the extent that we collect certain demographic information about you, we may use this information in
our market research, but we will do so only after we “anonymize” or “pseudonymize” the data, i.e.,
remove information that would confirm your identity. We will not use your personal data, however, to
send commercial or marketing messages to you unless we have a legal basis for doing so, such as your
consent or a contract with us for which, in either case, you will have the ability to opt out of by sending
an email to info@immunotec.com
This Site does not collect personal data when you browse the Site and request pages from our servers
unless you voluntarily and knowingly provide such information to us. This means that we will not know
your name, your email address, or any other personal data just because you browse the Site unless you:

     •   access the Site from a link in an email that we have sent to you;
     •   have created a profile and you either log-in to your account or choose to be remembered via your
         cookie or your web-enabled mobile device.
In these cases we will know who you are based on the information you previously supplied to us. When
you request a page from our Site, our servers log the information provided in the HTTP request header
including the IP number, the time of the request, the URL of your request and other information that is
provided in the HTTP header. We collect the HTTP request header information in order to make our Site
function correctly and provide you the functionality that you expect to see. We also use this information
to personalize content presented to you, better understand how visitors use our Site and how we can
better tune it, its contents, and functionality to meet your needs. We only use your personally identifiable
information for those activities listed at the time you submit your information to us. For example, if you
provide us with an email to inform you of special events, then that is what we will use your email address
to do. If we would like to use your personally identifiable information for an unrelated activity, we will
first request your consent to do so.
3.       Who Can Use the Information We Collect and How?
We may provide your personal data to third parties, or third parties may collect personal data from you
on our behalf if we have contracted with that third party to provide some part of the information or
service that you have requested. Other than those who act on our behalf and except as explained in this
Policy, personal data you provide at this Site will not be transferred to unrelated third parties, unless we
have a legal basis to do so. However, please note that personal data provided to this Site is subject to
disclosure pursuant to judicial or other government subpoenas, warrants or orders. We will only provide
this information after approximately two weeks following receipt of a valid subpoena or other legal
process in a civil case.
4.       How Do We Protect the Personal Information We Collect?
Security of Personal Data
We are committed to protecting the security of your personal data. Depending on the circumstances, we
may hold your information in hard copy and/or electronic form. For each medium, we use technologies
and procedures to protect personal data. We review our strategies and update as necessary to meet our
business needs, changes in technology, and regulatory requirements. We take our security obligations
seriously and so should you. While we are responsible for maintaining the security of this Site, you must
also access and use this Site in a manner that is responsible and secure. We adhere to internationally
recognized security standards and our information security management system relating to client
confidential data is independently certified as complying with the requirements of ISO/IEC 27001: 2013.
In addition, we have implemented a series of policies, procedures, and training to address data protection,
confidentiality, and security, and we update and review the appropriateness of these measures on a
regular basis.
Storage and Transfer of Personal Data
Personal data collected by Immunotec, Inc. may be stored and processed in your region, in the United
States or in any other country where Immunotec, Inc., its affiliates or contractors maintain facilities,
including outside the European Union. We take steps to ensure that the data we collect under this Privacy

Policy is processed pursuant to the terms thereof and the requirements of applicable law wherever the
data is located.
Immunotec, Inc. also collaborates with third parties such as cloud hosting services and suppliers located
around the world to serve the needs of our business, workforce, and customers. In some cases, we may
need to disclose or transfer your personal data within Immunotec, Inc. or to third parties in areas outside
of your home country. When we do so, we take steps to ensure that personal data is processed, secured,
and transferred according to applicable law.
If you would like to know more about our data transfer practices, please contact info@immunotec.com.
Retention of Personal Data
Immunotec, Inc. retains personal data for as long as necessary to provide the services and fulfill the
transactions you have requested, or for other business purposes such as complying with our legal
obligations, resolving disputes, and enforcing our agreements. We are required by law to keep some types
of information for certain periods of time (e.g., statute of limitations). If your personal data is no longer
necessary for the legal or business purposes for which it is processed, we will generally destroy or
anonymize that information.
5.         What Are Your Rights Regarding Your Personal Data?
We respect your right to access and control your personal data. You have choices about the data we
collect. When you are asked to provide personal data that is not necessary for the purposes of providing
you with our Sites, Products and Services, you may decline. However, if you choose not to provide data
that is necessary to provide a Service, you may not have access to certain features, Sites, Products, or
Services.
We aim to keep all personal data that we hold accurate, complete and up-to-date. While we will use our
best efforts to do so, we encourage you to tell us if you change your contact details. If you believe that
the information we hold about you is incorrect, incomplete or out-of-date, please contact
info@immunotec.com.
Access to personal data: In some jurisdictions, you have the right to request access to your personal data.
In these cases, we will comply, subject to any relevant legal requirements and exemptions, including
identity verification procedures. Before providing data to you, we will ask for proof of identity and
sufficient information about your interaction with us so that we can locate any relevant data. We may
also charge you a fee for providing you with a copy of your data (except where this is not permissible
under local law).
Correction and deletion: In some jurisdictions, you have the right to correct or amend your personal data
if it is inaccurate or requires updating. You may also have the right to request deletion of your personal
data. Please note that such a request could be refused because your personal data is required to provide
you with the products or services you requested, e.g. to deliver a product or send an invoice to your email
address, or that it is required by the applicable law.
Portability: If you reside within the European Union, you have the right to ask for a copy of your personal
data and/or ask for it to be ported to another provider of your choice. Please note that such a request
could be limited to the only personal data you provided us with or that we hold at that given time and
subject to any relevant legal requirements and exemptions, including identity verification procedures.

Marketing preferences: If you have provided us with your contact information, we may, subject to any
applicable Spam Act or similar regulation, contact you via email, postal mail or telephone about
Immunotec, Inc. products, services and events that may be of interest to you, including newsletters.
E-mail communications you receive from Immunotec, Inc. will generally provide an unsubscribe link
allowing you to opt-out of receiving future email or to change your contact preferences. E-mail
communications may also include a link to directly update and manage your marketing preferences. If you
have an online account with Immunotec, Inc., You can also change your contact preferences through your
account settings. Please remember that even if you opt out of receiving marketing emails, we may still
send you important Service information related to your accounts.
6.        How Do You Opt-out of Personal Information Sharing with Our Business Partners?
We may use third party analytics vendors to evaluate and provide us with information about the use of
our Services and viewing of our content. Some of the information you see on our Sites may be customized
based on automated predictions about your interests, which predictions are generated from your visits
over time and across different websites, using tools such as Google Analytics. This information allows us
to create content of greater interest to you and can also be used to serve ads based on your past visits to
our Sites. Note that you can opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies, including use by Google, by
visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page (http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/).
For more information about             how    targeted Network Advertising works, please visit:
http://www.youradchoices.com/           or     http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-
advertising.
You may opt-out of third party targeted advertising or analytics in two ways: 1) By directly notifying a
Network Advertising service provider via its opt-out tools (Please see above), or 2) using your browser’s
Do Not Track (DNT) settings to indicate that you do not wish to receive targeted advertising based on your
overall internet usage. For more information about DNT and how it works, please visit the Future of
Privacy Forum’s website: http://www.allaboutdnt.com/.
We will make a good faith reasonable effort to honor your DNT browser settings for opting out of receiving
targeted third party advertising based on your overall Internet usage. Please note that various browsers
frequently update technology or change their settings and business practices without advance notice, and
we may not have the latest information on how to honor your preferences. If you exercise either opt-out
option – the cookie opt-out or the browser opt-out – you will continue to receive advertising, but such
advertising may not relate to your specific interests, previous purchases, or search history.
However, you cannot opt-out of our contextual analytics and advertising, which is based on your usage of
only our Services. We will continue to serve you contextual advertising. We will also continue to monitor
your usage and search or transaction history to provide us with analytics on how well our Services,
features, and activities are functioning and used. We will also share this information in an aggregated or
anonymized form (meaning that no one individual person can be identified) within our company.
You can also opt out of our marketing emails at any time by contacting us at info@immunotec.com or by
sending us a post card to “OPT OUT”, Immunotec, Inc., 300 Joseph-Carrier, Vaudreuil-Dorion, Quebec,
Canada J7V 5V5.
7.        How Do You Correct and Update Your Personal Data?

You can change or correct your account information at any time. Just send an email with your old
information and your corrections to info@immunotec.com with "Correction" in the subject line.
8.       What is Our Privacy Policy If You Are an Underage Child?
We understand the importance of protecting the privacy of all individuals, especially the very young. Our
services are intended for United States audiences over the age of 18. Our Site and its Services are not
directed to children, and you may not use our Services if you are under the age of 13. You must also be
old enough to consent to the processing of your personal data in your country (in some countries we may
allow your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf). You must be at least 16 years of age to use the
Site Forums. Subscribing to our Services is restricted to adults who are either 18 years of age or older or
as otherwise legally defined by the country of your residency.
9.       What Happens When You Link to a Third-Party Web Site?
If you click on a link and go to another site, you will be subject to that website’s privacy policy. We
encourage you to read the posted privacy policy statement at any website before submitting any personal
data at all.
10.      What Happens When We Update Our Privacy Policy?
We may on occasion update our Privacy Policy. Your acceptance of any minor changes to this Privacy
Policy is indicated by your continued use of our Services. If we make any material changes to our Privacy
Policy, we will post a notice about the change at a prominent location on our Site. We encourage you to
periodically review our Site and this Privacy Policy for any changes.
11.      Your European Union Privacy Rights
If you are in the European Union, under the General Data Protection Regulation (Regulation EU 2016/679)
(also known as GDPR), you may have certain rights as a data subject. A data subject is a person who can
be identified by a name, identification number, location, online identifier, or other physical, physiological,
genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of the person. Under the GDPR, personal data is
information that relates to a data subject. The processing of your data is either based on your consent or
in case the processing is necessary for the performance of a contract to which you are a party, or in order
to take steps at your request prior to entering into a contract, cf. GDPR art. 6(1)(a)-(b). If the processing
is based on your consent, you may at any time withdraw your consent by contacting us at
info@immunotec.com
In order to enter into a contract to use our Services, you must provide us with the required personal data.
If you do not to provide us with all the required information, it will not be possible to deliver the Service.
To request information about or avail yourself of those rights, please send an email to
info@immunotec.com with "GDPR Request" in the subject line. In the email please describe, with
specificity, the GDPR right you are requesting assistance with. Please note additional information may be
requested prior to initiation of a request and that Immunotec, Inc. reserves the right to charge a fee with
respect to certain requests. Upon Immunotec, Inc.’s completion of its review you will be notified if your
request has been granted, denied, or exemptions apply.
12.      Your California Privacy Rights

If you are a California resident and have an established business relationship with us and want to receive
information about how to exercise your third party disclosure choices, you must send a request to the
following address with a preference on how our response to your request should be sent (email or postal
mail). You may contact us in two ways. Send email to info@immunotec.com
For requests sent via email, you must put the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” in the subject
field of your email. All requests sent via postal mail must be labeled “Your California Privacy Rights” on
the envelope or post card and clearly stated on the actual request. For all requests, please include your
name, street address, city, state, and zip code. (Your street address is optional if you wish to receive a
response to your request via email. Please include your zip code for our own recordkeeping.) We will not
accept requests via the telephone or by facsimile. We are not responsible for responding to notices that
are not labeled or not sent properly, or do not have complete information.
If you are a California resident under the age of 18, and a registered user of any site where this policy is
posted, California Business and Professions Code Section 22581 permits you request and obtain removal
of content or information you have publicly posted. To make such a request, please send an email with a
detailed description of the specific content or information to info@immunotec.com. Please be aware that
such a request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information you
have posted and that there may be circumstances in which the law does not require or allow removal
even if requested.
13.      What Else Do You Need To Know?
The Data Controller and Processor for Personal Data
A Data Controller is a company that collects people’s personal data and makes decisions about what to
do with it. A Data Processor is a person or company that deals with personal data as instructed by a Data
Controller for specific purposes and services. The Data Controller’s information is as follows:
COMPANY NAME IMMUNOTEC INC
ADDRESS 300 Joseph-Carrier, Vaudreuil-Dorion, Quebec, Canada J7V 5V5
EMAIL info@immunotec.com
PHONE 1-888-462-3397
The Data Processor’s information is as follows:
COMPANY NAME Exigo
ADDRESS 8130 John W. Carpenter Freeway
CITY, STATE, ZIP Dallas, TX 75247
EMAIL abuse@EXIGO.com
PHONE 214 367 9933
The Purpose and Legal Basis for Collection
Under the GDPR, there must be a lawful basis for processing personal data. There are six lawful bases,
and they are consent, contract, legal obligation, vital interests, public task, and legitimate interests. As
part of our compliance with the GDPR, we intend to use your personal data for the purpose of
Communications regarding news, updates and promotions. Our lawful basis for collecting and
processing your personal data is enrollment sign up. For more information, see Section 2 of our Privacy
Policy above.

The Legitimate Interest
In Company’s adherence with the GDPR, we have a legitimate interest which allows us to process your
personal data. This legitimate interest To keep you informed of all relevant and important
information regarding the company, your purchases and participating, and your account.
Recipients of Your Data and Categories of Data Collected
For more information, see Section 3 of our Privacy Policy above.
Data Protection Officer
Company is headquartered in CITY, STATE, COUNTRY. The Company has appointed ROBERT FELTON an
internal Data Protection Officer/ the following contact person for you to contact if you have any questions
or concerns about the Company’s personal data policies or practices. The Company’s Data Protection
Officer’s/Contact’s name and contact information are as follows:
COMPANY NAME Immunotec Inc.
ADDRESS Immunotec, Inc., 300 Joseph-Carrier, Vaudreuil-Dorion, Quebec, Canada J7V 5V5.
EMAIL info@immunotec.com
PHONE 1-888-462-3397
Transferring personal data from the EU to the US or other jurisdictions
The Company has its headquarters in Vaudreuil-Dorion, Quebec, Canada J7V 5V5. Personal data we
collect from you will be processed in the United States. The United States has not sought nor received a
finding of “adequacy” from the European Union under Article 45 of the GDPR. The Company relies on
derogations for specific situations as set forth in Article 49 of the GDPR. In particular, the Company collects
and transfers to the U.S. personal data only: with your consent; to perform a contract with you; or to
fulfill a compelling legitimate interest of the Company in a manner that does not outweigh your rights and
freedoms. The Company endeavors to apply suitable safeguards to protect the privacy and security of
your personal data and to use it only consistent with your relationship with the Company and the practices
described in this Privacy Policy. The Company also minimizes the risk to your rights and freedoms by not
collecting or storing sensitive information about you.
The 8 Rights of Individuals
Under the GDPR, You will benefit from increased rights including:
1.         The right to be informed
The right to be informed encompasses the obligation to provide you with ‘fair processing information.’ It
emphasizes the need for transparency over how your personal data is used.
2.         The right of access
Under the GDPR, you will have the right to obtain confirmation that your data is being processed, access
to your personal data, and other supplementary information.

3.      The right to rectification
You are entitled to have your personal data rectified if it is inaccurate or incomplete.
4.      The right to erasure
The right to erasure is also known as ‘the right to be forgotten.’ You may request the deletion or removal
of personal data where there is no compelling reason for its continued processing.
5.      The right to restrict processing
We are permitted to store your personal data, but not further process it without consent.
6.      The right to data portability
The right to data portability allows you to obtain and reuse your personal data for your own purposes
across different services. You may move, copy or transfer personal data easily from one IT environment
to another in a safe and secure way, without hindrance to usability.
7.      The right to object
You have the right to object to processing based on legitimate interests or the performance of a task in
the public interest/exercise of official authority (including profiling), direct marketing (including profiling);
and processing for purposes of scientific/historical research and statistics.
8.      Rights in relation to automated decision making and profiling
The GDPR provides safeguards for you against the risk that a potentially damaging decision is taken
without human intervention.
14.     What If You Have Questions?
If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact us via email at
info@immunotec.com.

                                                Cookie Policy
This site, like many others, uses small files called cookies to help us customize your experience. Find
out more about cookies and how you can control them.
This page contains information on what cookies are, the cookies used by the Immunotec, Inc. ("us," “we,”
“our,” or “Company”) website, how to switch cookies off in your browser, how to specifically switch off
advertising cookies, and some useful links for further reading on the subject. If it does not provide the
information you were looking for, or you have any further questions about the use of cookies on the
Company website, please email info@immunotec.com
What are cookies?
Cookies are small text files that are stored by the browser (for example, Internet Explorer or Safari) on
your computer or mobile phone. They allow websites to store things including your user preferences.
Think of cookies as providing a ‘memory’ for the website, so that it can recognize you when you come
back and respond appropriately.
How do we use cookies?
On our Site, you may encounter the following types of cookie:
Site performance cookies
Anonymous analytics cookies
Geotargetting cookies
Registration cookies
Advertising cookies
Third party advertising cookies
Site performance cookies
This type of cookie remembers your preferences for tools found on the Company’s website, so you don’t
have to re-set them each time you visit. Examples include:
– Volume settings for our video player
– Whether you see new content first
– Video streaming speeds that are compatible with your browser
Anonymous analytics cookies:
Every time someone visits our website, software provided by another organization generates an
“anonymous analytics cookie.” These cookies can tell us whether or not you have visited the site before.

Your browser will tell us if you have these cookies and, if you don’t, we generate new ones. This allows
us to track how many individual users we have, and how often they visit the site.
Unless you are signed in to the Site, we cannot use these cookies to identify individuals. We use them to
gather statistics, for example, the number of visits to a page. If you are logged in, we will also know the
details you gave to us for this, such as your username and email address.
Geotargetting cookies
These cookies are used by software which tries to work out what country you are in from the information
supplied by your browser when you click on a web page. This cookie is completely anonymous, and we
only use it to help target our content – such as whether you see a country specific home page – and
advertising.
Registration cookies
When you register with us, we generate cookies that let us know whether you are signed in or not. Our
servers use these cookies to work out which account you are signed in with, and if you are allowed access
to a particular service. It also allows us to associate any comments you post with your username. If you
have not selected “keep me signed in”, your cookies get deleted when you either close your browser or
shut down your computer. While you are signed into either of the sites, we combine information from
your registration cookies with analytics cookies, which we could use to identify which pages you have
seen.
Advertising cookies
These cookies allow us to know whether or not you’ve seen a particular ad or a type of advertisement,
and how long it is since you’ve seen it. We also use cookies to help us use targeted advertising. We may
use cookies set by another organization so we can more accurately target advertising to you. These
cookies are anonymous – they store information about what you are looking at on our site, but not about
who you are.
Third party advertising cookies
Some content you see on the Site is provided by other organizations. Some of these organizations use
their own anonymous cookies to track how many people have seen a particular ad, or to track how many
people have seen it more than once. The companies that generate these cookies have their
own privacy policies, and we have no access to read or write these cookies. These organizations may use
their cookies to anonymously target advertising to you on other websites, based on your visit to the Site.
Other third party cookies
On some pages of our website, other organizations may also set their own anonymous cookies. They do
this to track the success of their application, or to customize the application for you. Because of how

cookies work, our website cannot access these cookies, nor can the other organization access the data in
cookies we use on our website.
How do I turn cookies off?
It is usually possible to stop your browser accepting cookies, or to stop it accepting cookies from a
particular website. However, we cannot tell if you are signed in without using cookies, so you would not
be able to post comments.
All modern browsers allow you to change your cookie settings. You can usually find these settings in the
Options or Preferences menu of your browser. To understand these settings, the following links may be
helpful, or you can use the Help option in your browser for more details.
Cookie settings in Internet Explorer
Cookie settings in Firefox
Cookie settings in Chrome
Cookie settings in Safari web and iOS.
If you are primarily concerned about third party cookies generated by advertisers, you can turn these off
by going to the Your Online Choices site.
You can also visit the trade body representing these advertising platforms for more information: Network
Advertising Initiative.
Useful links
If you would like to find out more about cookies and their use on the Internet, you may find the following
links useful:
Microsoft Cookies guide
All About Cookies
The IAB has provided the following website to give information specifically about privacy issues around
Internet advertising:
youronlinechoices.co.uk/uk
For further legal information about privacy issues, you may find these links useful:
Data Protection Act 1998
The Information Commissioner’s Office
If you would like to contact us about cookies please email us: info@immunotec.com
